homemadebdsm.com 2018-05-23

# Privacy Statement - HOMEMADE BDSM

Privacy Statement  
  
Personal Information

HomeMadeBDSM.com allows you to visit the website without revealing any personal information about yourself. Your visit to this website is anonymous. We will only collect your contact information (first name, last name, billing address, phone number, email address and any other relevant information provided by you) as well as financial information (account or credit card numbers), with your permission and for the sole purpose of processing orders.

The information you provide will not be used for any commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners who adhere to HomeMadeBDSM.com's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. HomeMadeBDSM.com may provide your personal information if necessary, in HomeMadeBDSM.com�s good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of HomeMadeBDSM.com or others.

Security Procedures and Credit Cards

In order to provide secure processing of your credit card when ordering, HomeMadeBDSM.com uses Secure Server Software (SSL) that is among the best in use today by e-commerce Web sites. Your personal information, including sensitive credit card information, is encrypted so that it is indecipherable by others as it travels across the Internet. 

No credit card data is stored in HomeMadeBDSM.com's Customer Database

. All individual contact information provided to HomeMadeBDSM.com is stored in secure facilities.

Cookies

Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer in order to facilitate your next visit to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many web sites use them. HomeMadeBDSM.com does not use cookies that persist on your hard-drive. We do use dynamic, non-intrusive session cookies, which reside in your browser's memory only for the duration of your user session, to assist in the ordering and purchasing process. HomeMadeBDSM.com also uses data collected through session cookies for the purpose of identifying the source of traffic (which ad or link you used to reach us), and general patterns of activity on our site. No personally identifiable information is stored in this cookie. HomeMadeBDSM.com uses this data to better understand what services and support is valuable to our customers, and how we can continue to provide the best online experience possible to our users.

Links to Other Sites

Our site provides links to external web sites. HomeMadeBDSM.com does not monitor or control the content of such web sites or whether such web sites collect or process your personal data. When you click on one of those links, you leave our site and enter one that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. HomeMadeBDSM.com assumes no liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review their separate privacy policies.

Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using the web site or any services provided through the web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. HomeMadeBDSM.com may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Website. Your continued use of HomeMadeBDSM.com Software or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of these changes.

Support

HomeMadeBDSM.com provides email support for users who purchase the software at our Helpdesk. HomeMadeBDSM.com does not currently provide telephone support. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please [contact Us]() through email. We will do our best to respond to your inquiry within four business days.  
  
Find your Alternative playmate!   
| 

HD

[ siswet19](https://chaturbate.com/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=siswet19) 23

  * Bra off at goal #lovense is on! Tip #500 for french kissing Goal reached : bra off #lovense #squirt #ohmibod

  * 25 mins, 15158 viewers

| 

HD

[ murmur_kati](https://chaturbate.com/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=murmur_kati) 27

  * hot roll the dice 200 tk/neighbor asked to look after his daughter, I found out she a - Goal is : oil show and we panties off #lovense #ohmibod #interactivetoy #cum #squirt #hot #18 #natural #yang #blon

  * 33 mins, 7669 viewers

| 

HD

[ shackle_shot](https://chaturbate.com/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=shackle_shot) 26

  * SQUIRT SHOW STARTS AT GOAL. TIP 100 TO make it RAIN OR SHINE #lovense s at your service #hd #anal #squirt [4458 tokens remaining]

  * 13 mins, 4506 viewers

| 

HD

[ wh4thefuck](https://chaturbate.com/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=wh4thefuck) 99

  * Sneaky, Naughty, outside!!!! #lickmegood #edgetime #hotmoans ! Lovense On if you want to give me a wet time. 66, 77,88 Fun Numbers//201-Oil BOOBS, 202 - Multi-Goal : Hello Perv!!)) #lovense #ohmibod #i

  * 37 mins, 4502 viewers

| 

HD

[ sexycreolyta4u](https://chaturbate.com/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=sexycreolyta4u) 25

  * Make me HAPPY # lovense lush #pussy #ass #anal #torture me #make me cum - Multi-Goal : make me squirt #lovense

  * 22 mins, 4380 viewers

---|---|---|---|---
